[BEA] Ma…
Please, don't do that again.
Remember what I told you? I'll find a way.
I promise you.
I'll get back at Billy.
[BILLY] They may be delusional.
They believe in
their own version of the truth.
Bea has to pay for what she did.
- I told you--
- Well?
You still haven't found my grandpa?!
[MAN] Sir, we're very, very sorry.
But we're still looking for him.
We are looking for him, sir.
Jordan!
Dude, I can't find him!
Please, I can't lose him too.
Jordan, breathe. Breathe.
Let's split up so we can find him faster.
I'll go this way, you go that way.
Breathe, we'll find him.
- Thank you.
- [WOMAN] Sure.
Grandpa! Grandpa Jude!
Hi, Grandpa!
Are you okay?
I saw my son-in-law again.
He's not a good husband.
And he's not a good father either.
But he's tried to reach out several times.
It got me thinking.
What if he came back
because he has changed?
Who am I to deny my grandson's right
to see his father?
My grandson grew up
with hatred for his father.
It's hard to live
with resentment in your heart.
My parents disowned me when I was a kid.
Life was hard because I was alone.
But everything changed
when I met this girl.
So I'll marry her
once I find a way to escape from here.
[LAUGHS]
Oliver.
You're not going to school.
Why?
Your sister and I need to make sure
that your father
is no longer working there.
[OLIVER] I'm going.
[PRECIOUS]
Oliver, you're not.
Pa?
[OLIVER] Why did you leave us?
I made mistakes, son.
I admit it.
I wasn't a good father.
I love you and Billy, both of you.
I'd do anything to earn your forgiveness.
[SOBS SOFTLY]
Pa…
I already forgave you.
And besides,
I told you, remember?
I'll help you.
Billy has a good heart,
even if she can be a tiger sometimes.
[CHUCKLING]
- You got that from Billy.
- Yes.
She was the first one
to teach me self-defense.
Is that why you punched Biboy?
It wasn't just that, Pa.
She also talked back to Biboy's dad.
She didn't back down at all!
Ready to go, Auntie?
[ENRICO] Think you can do that?
- [OLIVER] Sure I can.
- [ENRICO] Bullseye both times!
[OLIVER] Did those two boys cry?
That must've hurt, huh?
You're sure about this, Billy?
You don't want Oliver to go home for now?
What else can I do, Auntie?
He's so stubborn. Such an obstinate kid!
Wonder where he got that from?
Well, at least he knows
how to fight for what he wants.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING]
He's growing up, Auntie Pres.
He makes his own choices now.
You okay with this?
For now.
Look how happy he was with his dad.
I can't take that away from him, Auntie.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Billy is really cool.
That's why everyone's intimidated by her.
Sometimes, I am too.
Only sometimes?
- Actually, all the time.
- [BOTH CHUCKLING]
But you know, Pa?
When it comes to Auntie,
she folds so fast.
[CHUCKLES] Oh, by the way.
Your sister and your auntie
should know that you're here.
They'll be worried about you for sure.
But, Pa,
they'll stop me from meeting up
with you again.
You know, Oliver,
you have to understand them.
You did nothing wrong.
I'm the one who's to blame here.
So you need to understand
where they're coming from.
Don't be mad at them.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING, FADES]
[GROANS]
Dear.
- Ma.
- Where's your laundry?
I'll do the laundry.
No need. I'll do it myself.
Let me do it. Just go to work.
And won't you get your paycheck already?
I will, Ma. Don't worry.
I'll pester them about it.
- I'll get to work then.
- All right. Be careful.
I will.
- [FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES]
[ZIPPER OPENS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hm?
[RINGING CONTINUES]
Hello?
Sorry, Billy.
I ducked out.
We know.
[BILLY] You're in school, right?
Yes.
I went to see Papa.
But I'll be going home soon.
Auntie Pres and I are here at the school.
Huh?
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING, FADES]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[GASPS] Really, Dad? For me?
Yes, that is my graduation gift for you!
- Thank you, Daddy!
- Happy?
- Of course!
- Let's go eat!
[CUSTOMER] Miss!
Miss, I bought this from you yesterday.
It's so slow. Why is that?
Hey, miss!
Miss, I'm talking to you! Hello?
- [CUSTOMER] What's the deal?
- Are you in a rush, huh?
Can't you wait? Is there
a taxi waiting for you?
- [GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [PHONE BUSY TONE]
[SNIFFLING]
- What's with this thing?
Look. The battery drains so fast.
I installed one app and look, it froze!
What's up?
- Look.
- Miss.
Maybe the problem is with
the app you installed.
This phone is brand new.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE BUSY TONE]
[SCREAMS]
[SOBBING]
[SCREAMING AND WAILING]
[PHONE CLATTERING]
The phone isn't the problem!
You know what the problem is?!
That annoying app!
My goodness…
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[SLAMS COUNTER]
Billy, Auntie.
[BILLY] Hm.
[SOFTLY] Auntie…
Billy, I'm sorry for leaving
without letting you know.
We got so worried.
Don't do it again, okay?
Okay, Auntie.
Billy, can I--
Let's talk at home.
So I don't have to go home yet?
Yeah, you can still make it
to your next class.
Here are your things.
Go on then.
Bye-bye, Billy, Auntie!
I'll see him off.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
So when Mr. Fabrizio arrives,
he'll ask us if we're ready
for a global rollout for sure.
We're more than ready.
- The servers are already multi-regional.
- [WHISPERS] Okay.
Even if the users overseas
sign up all at the same time,
we're on par.
Good.
I'm sure he'll ask you,
"What makes LoveList different
from the other swiping apps?"
[CLICKS FINGERS]
Hmm…
- Well…
- [BILLY] Mm-hmm.
We're not just swipe-based.
Our matching engine is behavior-driven.
Mm-hmm.
It learns from conversations,
activity patterns,
as well as response timing.
So as people use the app,
the matches become more accurate.
Very good.
That's exactly what he needs to hear.
Yes, boss.
[PHONE CHIMES]
Okay.
Here we go.
- He's arriving in 15 minutes.
- [CLEARS THROAT]
[BILLY] Whoo.
[BILLY EXHALES]
[HUFFS]
What?
Do I have something on my face?
- What?
- It's not that.
I'm just thinking…
How do you do that?
Like, compartmentalizing.
So easy to just turn off a problem,
focus on another…
It's like you don't even think about…
About what?
About Oliver.
Hmm.
That he's already talking to your father.
I just didn't expect that
you'd let him.
You know, I just gave Oliver what--
What he wanted?
What he needed.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
I kept it a secret from him for years.
Because I wanted to protect him.
But you know, dude,
when I saw him with that man,
I felt guilty.
So no matter how angry I was at him,
I knew I was wrong to decide for Oliver.
It was wrong for me
to make decisions for him.
Because all he wants is to know his dad.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Dude, are you convinced that
your dad is truly remorseful?
This isn't about him anymore, dude.
This is all about Oliver now.
Okay.
So, what's your plan?
Get out of here!
I'll take care of things here.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Mr. Dino.
Good morning.
Why'd you choose to join our group?
I just wanted to talk to you guys.
I just wanted to share.
My officer said…
I should behave
because it might reduce my sentence.
And from what I can see,
you're the nicest people here.
What do you know?
Nothing.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
What do you know?
[STAMMERS] N-Nothing.
Is there something I should know?
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
LoveList was built in the Philippines,
but the chase for real connection
is not uniquely Filipino.
It's universal.
Our mindset is global
from day one, Mr. Fabrizio.
Well, you all know me as a lawyer.
I run a firm with my wife,
and on the side, I also invest in tech.
Especially, platforms that can be scaled,
not just locally,
but also internationally.
And that's why this
really caught my attention.
You see, my daughter's in her twenties
and her entire social life happens
on apps like this.
That's why when you sent me the proposal,
it completely made sense.
It didn't feel like
just like any other pitch.
Of course, we did our due diligence,
but from the very start,
I could see its full potential.
LoveList was designed
exactly for users like her.
Active, open to real connections,
looking for something meaningful.
[PETER] Right.
So let's say…
[CLEARS THROAT]
…we onboard
three to five million new users
within the first six months
after international launching.
How does this affect
your backend architecture?
Do you have a projected infrastructure
cost per additional million? Or…?
Well, from the start,
it's really built for that.
- Right.
- It's based on
a cloud system that grows with demand.
So we don't have to stop and rebuild
every time there's a traffic spike.
Uh, we've run the numbers too.
We know what it takes.
- Mm-hmm.
- We're ready.
One more question then.
Um, what makes LoveList different
from all the other swipe apps?
Good question.
Well, LoveList isn't based on swipes.
Our matching engine is driven by
how the users behave online.
The system tracks how users interact.
We focus on behavior, not just profiles.
How the users talk, engage, respond.
That's where the real signal is.
So, over time,
the system gets to know the user,
and the quality of matches
improves naturally.
At the end of the day,
LoveList isn't just trying
to match people.
We're trying to get to know them more.
All right.
Well, after reviewing your proposal
and hearing you talk now…
I'm in.
I can see where this can go.
So, let's move forward.
I'll have my team coordinate
with the contracts.
Okay?
- Great. Great! Thank you.
- All right, thank you.
Thank you for the trust, Mr. Fabrizio.
Oh, please, just call me Peter.
- Thank you, Peter.
- All right.
- Of course.
Uh, Peter, can we have a photo with you?
Oh, yes. By all means.
- [MARJ] Okay. Girls, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Here?
- [BILLY] Hey, Morrie.
- Stay in the middle please.
- Oh, all right.
You can take the photo.
[WOMAN] All right.
- Smile! One, two, three.
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
Another one!
- One, two, three.
- [CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
- It's done.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Can you now kindly assist Mr. Fabrizio?
All right.
- I'll see you guys again.
- Okay, see you.
Thank you, sir.
- Take care.
- Thank you.
- [SCREAMING, APPLAUDING]
- We closed the deal!
- Good job!
- We did it!
Oh my God, it's happening!
You guys were amazing.
- Shh! He might still be here. Okay, quiet.
- Wait, Billy. Are you really okay now?
Are you really okay now?
- I'm okay.
- Are you sure?
I'm okay.
- [DELIGHTED LAUGH, RELIEVED SIGH]
- [OVERLAPPING HAPPY CHATTER]
Wow.
- Wow!
- [TONI] Nice one!
- [APPLAUDING]
- Congrats!
[INDISTINCT, HAPPY CHATTER
AND GUSHING]
Thanks, Lucy, for all your help.
I just hope wherever you end up,
you'll find a job.
Did the principal call you in?
I'm sorry you got dragged into my mess.
Dragged into it? Not at all.
But yeah, Ma'am Ronquillo talked to me.
I denied knowing that Oliver was your son.
But you know, I think
if your oldest daughter
talks to the principal,
she might change her mind.
She might reconsider.
I've accepted that Billy won't forgive me.
Okay, Billy.
All right, don't worry anymore.
I'll take care of it, okay?
I'll talk to your father.
Just make sure you're sure
about your decision, okay?
Okay. Bye, Billy.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[RINGING CONTINUES]
Precious?
Enrico, let's meet. We need to talk.
Ah, okay, okay.
Where? When?
Tonight at seven. Can you make it?
Okay, Enrico. Let's meet.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I hope you can
forgive me, Precious.
I never meant to hurt you.
I didn't come here
to listen to your explanation.
- But, Pres--
- Listen.
You can meet with Oliver.
But Billy said I have
to be there too.
If it wouldn't have
landed me in prison,
I would've killed them!
My husband and his lover!
What you're thinking is wrong.
You can't do that.
What about having an affair with
a married man? Is that right?
Are you sure about
your decision?
My brother's all grown up.
I just want to give him the chance
to meet his father,
even just for a little while.
I wish I had your courage.
[BILLY] You saw how happy
he was earlier, didn't you?
Didn't I tell you that decision
was for Oliver?
The boss is really in love.
- [JORDAN HUMMING]
- He's completely smitten.